<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Translation>
  <!-- 
    Increment the TranslationVersion every time the translation file is updated
	Also update the version.info file
  -->
  <TranslationVersion>0</TranslationVersion>
  <item>
    <key>Description</key>
    <value>Please select the search functions that {0} shall enhance.
	
{0} will perform the search in all open databases and will enrich the result shown with the database a found entry is contained in.

KeePass as well as many of the available plugins assume that all entries shown in the entry list are contained in the currently active database.
To not break compatibility and to avoid inconsistencies like flagging the wrong database as changed, {0} will behave as follows:

If a search returns results from multiple databases, the results will be shown in a separate window. 
Selecting an entry will
- Activate the selected entry's database
- Show all found entries in the entry list, that are contained in this database

If '{1}' returns only entries from exactly one database, this database will be activated and the search results will be shown as usual.</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>OptionsCaption</key>
    <value>Enhance searches</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>Search</key>
    <value>Search in all open databases</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>MultiDBSearchInfoSearchFormActive</key>
    <value>Show info if '{0}' returns entries from multiple databases</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>MultiDBSearchInfoSearchForm</key>
    <value>The result of this search contain entries from multiple databases and will be displayed in a separate window.
After selecting an entry, the entry list will show only found entries contained in the selected entry's database.

To disable this message, choose '{0}' or visit the plugin's options</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>MultiDBSearchInfoSingleSearchActive</key>
    <value>Show info if other searches return entries from multiple databases</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>MultiDBSearchInfoSingleSearch</key>
    <value>You selected an entry from a multi-db search result.
The entry list will show only found entries contained in the selected entry's database.

To disable this message, choose '{0}' or visit the plugin's options</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>ErrorNoActivation</key>
    <value>Activation of {0} not possible.

Could not find required objects</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>PWDisplayMode</key>
    <value>Password display</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>PWDisplayModeAlways</key>
    <value>Always</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>PWDisplayModeNever</key>
    <value>Never</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>PWDisplayModeEntryView</key>
    <value>Like Entry List</value>
  </item>
  <item>
    <key>UseEntryListColumnWidths</key>
    <value>Column widths like Entry List</value>
  </item>
</Translation>